Guide to Rice University Vice President of Finance and Administration office records, 1938-2010 UA 140
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University Vice President of Finance and Administration office records
1938-2010 (bulk 1980-2000)
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice University
UA 140
84 Linear Feet (122 boxes)
The Office of Finance and Administration generated these records from 1938-2010. Most of the records were created during the tenures of Dean W. Currie, vice president of Finance and Administration, and Neill Binford, associate vice president of Finance and Administration. At the time of these records, Finance and Administration included the departments of Facilities and Engineering, the Controller, Human Resources, Administrative Computing, Food and Housing, Office of the Associate Vice President, and the Budget Office. The vice president of Finance and Administration oversaw the infrastructure of the university, the food services in the colleges, the human resouces department and the police department.
Biographical / Historical
The Rice University Office of Finance and Administration generated these records from 1938-2010. Most of the records were created during the tenures of Dean W. Currie, vice president of Finance and Administration, and Niell Binford, associate vice president of Finance and Administration. At the time of these records, Finance and Administration included the departments of Facilities and Engineering, the Controller, Human Resources, Administrative Computing, Food and Housing, Office of the Associate Vice President, and the Budget Office. The vice president of Finance and Administration oversaw the infrastructure of the university, the food services in the colleges, the human resouces department and the police department.
Scope and Contents
The Rice University Office of Finance and Administration generated these records from 1938-2010. Most of the records were created during the tenures of Dean W. Currie, vice president of Finance and Administration, and Neill Binford, associate vice president of Finance and Administration. At the time of these records, Finance and Administration included the departments of Facilities and Engineering, the Controller, Human Resources, Administrative Computing, Food and Housing, Office of the Associate Vice President, and the Budget Office. The vice president of Finance and Administration oversaw the infrastructure of the university, the food services in the colleges, the human resouces department and the police department.
Access Restrictions
This material is restricted and requires permission from the Office of Finance and Administration for access. Contact the Woodson Research Center to learn more about the restrictions or about accessing the collection. Please call 713-348-2586 or e-mail woodson@rice.edu for more information.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored offsite at the Library Service Center and require 24-hour notice for retrieval. Please contact the Woodson Research Center at 713-348-2586 or woodson@rice.edu for more information.
Acquisition Information
Collection tranferred by the Office of Finance and Adminstration. Addendum transferred in 2012.
Index Terms
Subjects
Universities and colleges -- Administration; Universities and colleges
Document Types
notes; letters (correspondence); reports
Subjects (Corporations)
Rice University
- Series I: Administration, 1980-2002
  - Shepherd School of Music, 1975-1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Rice Trusts Inc., list of charitable trusts, August 1, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Building information summary, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Work papers 1985 Space utilization study (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Indirect cost study, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Physical inventory reconciled fiscal year ending June 30, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1987 Space Utilization Study; part 1 of 2 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1987 Space Utilization Study; part 2 of 2 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Space study --- soft changes from original studies, circa 1987 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Space utilization study room utilization to payroll expense comparisons, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 1987 Space utilization trial study; part 1 of 2 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 1987 Space utilization trial study; part 2 of 2 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Work papers 1987 space utilization study, February 23, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Neill Binford --- space measurements, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - use allowance allocation cost study, June 30, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Space utilization study, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Space utilization survey, June 1988 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Definition of space usage adn abbreviations, circa 1988 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Finance --- second closing and status report of funds, June 30, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Space utilization study department contracts, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Utility usage study; part 1 of 2, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Utility usage study; part 2 of 2, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Shepherd School building prgram - space analysis, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Utility usage, monthly-year to day, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Neill Binford --- centers and institutes, circa 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Neill Binford, buildings by capitalizaiton, 1989, no date (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Neill Binford --- EEOC [Equal Employment Opportunity Commission], May 3, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Neill Binford --- Registrar classrooms, current room list, circa 1989 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Neill Binford, space analysis, operating casts and related memos, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Neill Binford --- Space utilization and allocation memo, June 26, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Neill Binford --- Toxic buildings, floor plans, memos, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Vacant space; folder 1 of 3, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Vacant space; folder 2 of 3, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Vacant space; folder 3 of 3, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Space utilization study 1988-1989: academic records (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Space utilization study 1988-1989: administrative computing (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Space utilization Study 1988-1989: administrative store (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Space utilitzation study 1988-1989: admissions (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Space utilitzation study 1988-1989: affirmative action, EEOC (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Space Utilization Study 1988-1989: Alumni Association (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Space utilization study 1988-1989: Anthropology (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Space utilization study 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Space utilization study 1988-1989: art and art history (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Space utilization study 1988-1989: athletics (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Space utilization study 1988-1989: band (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Space utilization study 1988-1989: biochemistry (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Space utilization study 1988-1989: biology (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Space utilization study 1988-1989: biomedical engineering (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Space utilization study 1988-1989: bookstore (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Space utilization: biosciences and bioengineering, George R. Brown Hall, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Space utilization - Herman Brown Hall to Autry Court, 1988-1989 (Box 3)
  - Space utilization - Hamman Hall to Space allocation reports, 1989-1991 (Box 4)
  - Space utilization and space inventory, 1991-1995 (Box 5)
  - Space utilization and space inventory and campus police, 1995-2002 (Box 6)
  - Campus police incident reports (Box 7)
  - Campus police - Finance and Administration personnel (Box 9)
  - Finance and Administration personnel (Box 10)
  - Finance and Administration personnel (Box 11)
  - Finance and Administration personnel (Box 12)
  - Finance and Administration personnel - Committees: Academic Affairs, 1980-1989 (Box 13)
  - Committees: Audit - Buildings and Grounds, 1987-1991 (Box 14)
  - Committees: Buildings and Grounds, 1982-1992 (Box 15)
  - Committees: Buildings and Grounds, 1992-2002 (Box 16)
  - Committees: cable television - compliance, 1988-1995 (Box 17)
  - Committees: computer planning board, 1987-1990 (Box 18)
  - Committees: computer planning board, 1989-1992 (Box 19)
  - Committees: computer planning board, 1988-1990 (Box 20)
  - Committees: computer planning board - financial affairs, 1988-1990 (Box 21)
  - Committees: financial affairs - parking, 1990-2002 (Box 22)
  - Committees: parking - facilities planning board, 1993 (Box 23)
  - Committees: Collaborative Research Center proposals, 2004 (Box 25)
  - Committees: Collaborative Research Center, 2004 (Box 26)
  - Board of Governors: meetings, 1988-1991 (Box 27)
  - Board of Governors: meetings, 1991-1994 (Box 28)
  - Board of Governors, 1994-1999 (Box 29)
  - Board of Governors: book for Josephine Abercrombie; part 1, 1994 (Box 30)
  - Commission on Women: report on child care, 1992-1994 (Box 31)
  - Board of Governors: book for Josephine Abercrombie; part 2, 1994 (Box 32)
  - Parking study and Cesar Pelli's Master plan, 1999-2000 (Box 33)
  - Parking study, 1999-2000 (Box 34)
  - Off campus: associations - Bush Library, 1994 (Box 35)
  - Off campus: Cambridge Associates - Coopers and Lybrand, 1992-1995 (Box 36)
  - Off campus: CRSS - Harvard Business School (Box 37)
  - Off campus: Harvard information (Box 38)
  - Off campus: Harvard - March of Dimes (Box 39)
  - Off campus: Methodist Hospita - South Main Center Association (Box 40)
  - Off campus: South Main Center Association - Texas A (Box 41)
  - Off campus: Texas Energy and Natural Resources - YMCA of Rockies (Box 42)
  - On campus: Administrative store - campus lighting (Box 43)
  - On campus: Controller - Designated driver program (Box 44)
  - On campus: disabled faculty - key card system (Box 45)
  - On campus: KTRU - retirement contributions (Box 46)
  - Ryon Engineering Lab options for reuse - Wiess House (Box 47)
  - On campus departments: Athletics - telecommunications (Box 48)
  - On campus departments: Food and Housing's housing apartment project - annual reports, 1987-1992 (Box 49)
  - On campus departments: Economic Summit - KTRU radio station, 1986-1991 (Box 50)
  - departmental budgets, 1987 (Box 51)
  - KTRU - Reading file of Binford, N., 1986-1992 (Box 52)
  - Reading file of Binford, N. - Architecture, Fondren Library, 1992-1999 (Box 53)
  - Architecture: Humanities building - residential colleges, 1994-1998 (Box 54)
  - Architecture: Jones Business School - financial statements, 1999-2002 (Box 55)
- Series II: Finance, 1979-2000
  - Capital and maintenance projects and budget requests, 1979-1999 (Box 56)
  - General finance - Division 6 distribution, 1986-1993 (Box 57)
  - Budgets and capital related items, 1980-1995 (Box 58)
  - Budgets and capital related items (continued), 1980-1995 (Box 59)
  - Budgets, 1997-1998 (Box 60)
  - Capital projects, 1990-1991 (Box 61)
  - Operating budgets - Finance and Administration budgets, 1994-1995 (Box 62)
  - Capital and maintenance projects, 1979-1985 (Box 63)
  - Budget work papers - budget process (Box 64)
  - Division 6 budgets and academic budgets, 1990-1991 (Box 65)
  - Budgets - RUPD, 1994 (Box 66)
  - Budgets, 1990-1991 (Box 67)
  - Budgets (continued), 1990-1991 (Box 68)
  - Budgets (continued), 1989-1991 (Box 69)
  - Capital and major maintenance, 1991-1993 (Box 70)
  - Capital and major maintenance - Facilities and Engineering, 1988-1991 (Box 71)
  - Capital and major maintenance, 1988-1989 (Box 72)
  - Capital and major maintenance, 1987-1990 (Box 73)
  - Capital and major maintenance, 1986-1989 (Box 74)
  - Financial strategies and statements, 1980-1992 (Box 75)
  - Rice Trust, Inc., 1982-1992 (Box 76)
  - Computer tapes from Texas Commerce Bank for Rice University, 1997 (Box 77)
  - The Graduate Apartments Inc., bound in three volumes, 1998 (Box 78)
  - Travel expenses, 1996-2000 (Box 79)
  - Credit card expenditures, 1992-1993 (Box 80)
  - Credit card expenditures (continued), 1992-1993 (Box 81)
  - Receipts, April 1999 - December 1999 (Box 82)
  - Receipts, January 2000 - November 2000 (Box 83)
  - Architecture firm proposals/background information, 1991 - 2001 (Box 84)
  - Introductory briefs volumes 1 and 2, 1988 (Box 85)
- Series III: Dean Currie Finance and Administration, 1983 - 2004
  - Anderson M.D. Biological Labs, 1994 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Architecture: Anderson Hall, 1980-1986 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Architecture: Alice Pratt Brown Hall, 1987-1992 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Architecture: George R. Brown Hall, 1988-1992 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Architecture: Duncan Hall (Computational Engineering Building), 1996-1999 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Architecture: Herring Hall, 1982-1989 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Architecture: Ley/Rice Memorial Center, 1986-1988 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Architecture: Seeley G. Mudd Computer Science Lab, 1983 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Articles on Rice University Architecture, 1984-1992 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Baker Institute: Conference, 1995-1997 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Baker Institute: Correspondence, Publications, 1993-1997 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Baker Institute: Office Space and Building, 1994-1995 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Benches on Campus, No Date (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Budgets FYE, 1990-1992 (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Budgets FYE, 1993 (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Budgets FYE, 1994 (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - Budgets FYE, 1995 (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - Budgets FYE, 1996-1997 (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - Campus Construction Council, 2000 (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - Campus Growth by Decade, 1997 (Box 86, Folder 20)
  - Colleges: Bi Weekly Reports, 2000 (Box 86, Folder 21)
  - Colleges: Martel/Jones/Brown Monthly Progress Report, 2000 (Box 86, Folder 22)
  - Colleges: New College Construction Fact Sheet, No Date (Box 86, Folder 23)
  - Colleges: Ninth College, 1995-1998 (Box 86, Folder 24)
  - Colleges: SID Richardson Balconies, 1993-1994 (Box 86, Folder 25)
  - Colleges: South College, 1998 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Colleges: South College Brown and Root, 1999 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Colleges: South College Program Development, Costs, Schedule, 1998 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Colleges: Wiess College, 1996-2000 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Colleges: New Wiess College Monthly Progress Report, 2000 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Colleges: Wiess College Renovation Study, 1995 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Committees: Ad Hoc Security Access, 1995-1996 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Committees: Memberships and Mandates, 1999-2000 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Committees: Security, 2001-2003 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Committees: Space Facilities Planning Board, 1991-1995 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Committees: Space Facilities Planning Board, 1991-1993 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Committees: Wayfinding Signages, 2004 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Complaints, 1990-1992 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Comptroller, 1988-1991 (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Comptroller, 1992-1997 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education (COFHE) Conference Georgetown University, 1996 (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Cornerstones and Donor Plaques, 1996 (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - Cost Escalation in Universities-Duke, 1994 (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - Cost Escalation in Universities: The Escalation Costs of Higher Education, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 19)
  - Cost Escalation in Universities: Trends in Instituional Costs, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 20)
  - Easements, 1999 (Box 87, Folder 21)
  - Easements: Martel College - Issues, 2000 (Box 87, Folder 22)
  - Facilities: Buildings and Grounds Committee, 2003 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Facilities: Maintenance Report, 2001 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Facilities: Rice Air Emissions Compliance Strategy, 2001 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Facilities: Rice Capital Budget Report, 2004 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Facilities and Engineering: Founder's Room (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Financial Statements: PriceWaterHouseCoopers, 2003 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Financial Statements: Arthur Anderson, 1994 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Indirect Costs, 1993-1997 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Indirect Costs, 1992 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Indirect Costs, 1988-1991 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Indirect Costs: Federal Concepts, 1997 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Internal Revenue Service Part I, 1995-1997 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Internal Revenue Servive Part II, 1994-1995 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Investment, 1996-1997 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Investment, 1994-1995 (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - Investment Committee, 1997 (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - Investment: Management Studies Various Firms, 1996-1998 (Box 88, Folder 17)
  - Investment: Management Studies Various Firms, 1994-1995 (Box 88, Folder 18)
  - Investment: Managment Studies Various Firms, 1993-1994 (Box 88, Folder 19)
  - Jones School Dean Search, 1996-1997 (Box 88, Folder 20)
  - Library Service Center (South Annex), 2002 (Box 88, Folder 21)
  - Lovett Hall Floor Plans, 1993-1996 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Master Plan Studies/Pelli, 1999 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Master's House, 1990-1994 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Masters Report on Faculty Activity in the Colleges, No Date (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Minority Affairs, 1989-1999 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Minority Affairs: Richard Tapia, 1990-1993 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Minority Recruiting, 1994-1998 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Moore, Walter P., 1998 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Multicultural Affairs, 1994 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Music Library, 1999-2000 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Museum of Natural Science, Houston, 1995 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - National Youth Leadership Forum, 1994 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - Natural Gas, 1988-1989 (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - NCAA Athletics Certification Self-Study Report Part I, 1999 (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - NCAA Athletics Certification Self Study Report Part II, 1999 (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - New Building Projects Design Subcommittee Photographs, 2000 (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - New Building Projects Master Schedule, 1999 (Box 89, Folder 17)
  - Nicandros, Constantine (Dino), undated (Box 89, Folder 18)
  - NSF Research Facilities Survey, 1993-1995 (Box 89, Folder 19)
  - Old Chemistry Renovation, 1997-1999 (Box 89, Folder 20)
  - Ombuds Position, 1995 (Box 89, Folder 21)
  - Organizational Design, 1993 (Box 89, Folder 22)
  - Orientation Week, 1994-1998 (Box 89, Folder 23)
  - Owlnet, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 24)
  - Paradigm Shift, No Date (Box 89, Folder 25)
  - Parking Access and Revenue Control System, 2002 (Box 89, Folder 26)
  - Parking: Kimley-Horn Consultants Working Papers, undated (Box 89, Folder 27)
  - Parking Study: Rice University Kimley-Horn, undated (Box 89, Folder 28)
  - Pelli, Cesar and Associates: Master Plan for Growth, 1983-1999 (Box 89, Folder 29)
  - Physical Facilities in a Strategic Plan Needs and Costs, 1997 (Box 89, Folder 30)
  - Policies - Rice University, 1989-1995 (Box 89, Folder 31)
  - Policies: Rice University, 1995 (Box 89, Folder 32)
  - President's Report, 1986-2000 (Box 89, Folder 33)
  - Print Shop, 1995-1997 (Box 89, Folder 34)
  - Project Authorizations, 1998 (Box 89, Folder 35)
  - Public Affairs, 1999-2000 (Box 89, Folder 36)
  - Publicity Articles, 1990-1996 (Box 89, Folder 37)
  - Ryan, Frank VP For External Affairs, 1989-1994 (Box 89, Folder 38)
  - Sasaki Associates Correspondence, 1990-1997 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Sasaki Associates Landscape Vision and Design Guidelines, 1990-2000 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Sasaki Associates Rice University Residential College Master Plan, 1997 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Self Study, 1995 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Self Study Reports, 1995 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Self Study Support Services, 1994 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Sewall Hall Renovation Part I, 2001 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Sewall Hall Renovation Part II, 2001 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Space Data Report, 1998 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Space Inventory Online, 1996 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Space Planning: Application of Normative Space Guidelines, 1996 (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Space Planning: Application of Normative Space Guidelines, 1997 (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Space Planning: Bookstore, 1999 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - Space Planning: Classroom Project, 1998 (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - Space Planning: Classroom Study, 1996 (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - Space Planning: Classroom Study Appendix, 1996 (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - Space Planning: General Information, 1996-2000 (Box 90, Folder 17)
  - Space Planning: Jones School of Management, 1998 (Box 90, Folder 18)
  - Space Planning: Needs, 1989-1993 (Box 90, Folder 19)
  - Space Planning: Student Activities Center, 1992-1995 (Box 90, Folder 20)
  - Space Planning FYE 1998 Data (Box 90, Folder 21)
  - Space Planning Committee, 1996-1999 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Space Planning Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Space Planning Committee, 1993-1995 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Space Planning Committee (Space Facilities Planning Board), 1992 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Space Planning Committee (Space Facilities Planning Board) I, 1991 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Space Planning Committee (Space Facilities Planning Board) II, 1991 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Space Planning Committee (Space Facilities Planning Board), 1989-1990 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Space Planning Committee (Space Facilities Planning Board), 1988 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Space Study: Lou Griffin, undated (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Space Survey, 1989-1995 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Space Utilization By Department/Division, 1992-1995 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Strategic Plan: Implementing "Rice: The Next Century", 1997-1998 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Strategic Plan: Rice University: Setting the Standard, 1991 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Texas Higher Education Coordinating Board, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Tuition Strategies, 1994-1998 (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - Tuition: Student Tuition Committee, 1990-1996 (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - Tuition Waiver, 1994-1995 (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - Wiess School of Natural Sciences, 1997 (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - Willy's Pub, 1989-1997 (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - Y2K Problem, 1996-2000 (Box 91, Folder 20)
- Series IV: Neill Binford Finance and Administration, 1983 - 2004
  - Campus Planning and Development, 1983 - 1995 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Debt: 501 (c) (3), 1997 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Debt: Baker Botts, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Debt: Cambridge Associates Financial Indicators, 1994 - 1996 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Debt: Distribution list, 1999 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Debt: Gillis, "Sensible Use of Debt for Educational Purposes", 1998 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Debt: Goldman Sachs, 1998 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Debt: Goldman Sachs Presentations to Ratings Agencies, 1999 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Debt: Impact of Debt Policy Ratios, 1998 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Debt: Moody's Financing Colleges, 1999 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Debt: Morgan Stanley Debt Capacity Financing Alternatives for Rice University, 1998 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Debt: Rice University Debt Policy, 1998 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Debt: Salomon Smith Barney Capital Planning Materials, 1998 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Debt: SEI Asset Consulting Group Investment Policy, 1995 (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Debt: Trinity Real Estate Finance, 1999 (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Judicial Programs / Code of Student Conduct, 1996 - 1997 (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - Parking Advisory Committee, 1992 (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - Parking Advisory Committee Correspondence, 1992 - 1994 (Box 92, Folder 18)
  - Parking Advisory Committee Meeting Agendas I, 1992 - 1993 (Box 92, Folder 19)
  - Parking Advisory Committee Meeting Agendas II, 1991 - 1992 (Box 92, Folder 20)
  - Parking Garages, 1999 - 2003 (Box 92, Folder 21)
  - Parking Garages Study/Planning, 1998 - 2000 (Box 92, Folder 22)
  - Parking Study I, 1991 - 1993 (Box 92, Folder 23)
  - Parking Study II, 1991 (Box 92, Folder 24)
  - Parking Study: Jack Mitchell I, 1991 - 1992 (Box 92, Folder 25)
  - Parking Study: Jack Mitchell II, 1991 - 1995 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Policies (Outdated), 1973 - 1996 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Prepaid Tuition: Miller, Canfield, Paddock, Stone, 1998 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Prepaid Tuition Coalition, 1997 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - President's Office: Binford Presentation, 1994 - 1999 (Box 93, Folder 5)